MOTIVATED AND PROGRESSIVE SOFTWARE **DEVELOPER WITH STRONG** SKILLS IN SPRING BOOT/.NET

Laust Eberhardt Bonnesen

Click on a text to open its link:

Nørre boulevard 98, 1 tv. 4600 Køge **+**45 60548098

in laust-eberhardt-bonnesen

@ laustslaustede@gmail.com Caustrup



PROFILE

I am a 27-year-old software developer/engineer and QA tester who, in addition of being motivated and progressive, is resourceful, responsible and collaborative, with experience in implementing, maintaining, developing, debugging, analysing and designing fullstack code.

These characteristics about me, I find to be important in a work environment, in which code can be implemented with good elements such as reliability, stability and security, which can at the same time be user-friendly with a large selection of functions and the code must also have the possibility to continually be able to be further improved through scalability and readability with plenty of documentation.

SKILLS

Here are the different skills in categories within the different tools and knowledge I possess.

During the chapters experience and education, areas of these skills are further described.

FRAMEWORKS

.NET Spring **Spring Boot**

Maven Vue SwelteKit

React Native Vite Unity

PROJECTMANAGING

ΧP ITIL Scrum Waterfall

Test-driven **Event-driven**

LANGUAGES

Java C# JSON JavaScript

TypeScript C **VHDL** Verilog

DATABASE

MySQL MSSQL SQLite

MARKUP/STYLING

CSHTML JSP **HTML XML**

CSS

TESTING

Unit Acceptance Integration **JUnit** XUnit AAA

\mathbf{UML}

Domain Class ER Package

VERSION CONTROL

GitHub GitLab Git

ARCHITECTURE

MVC **GRASP SOLID**

CONTAINERS

Docker Kubernetes

CLOUD

Azure **AWS** Firebase CI/CD

COURSES

- Prosa Firewall and Filtering
- Prosa Kubernetes Security
- Prosa Secure Coding
- Prosa Introduction to Vue.is
- Jetbrain Java OAuth

Danish: Native speaking

Pilestræde 58, 1112 København

English: Fluent Swedish: Familiar German: Familiar Portuguese: Beginner

EXPERIENCE

Backend Intern | Infomedia

August 2022 - November 2022

· Used Scrum as agile project managing.

Worked within:

- Dapper - .NET Core with C# - Bulkcopy - MVC structured APIs

- MediatR - MSSQL

- Gained experience of working in a workplace together with other both skilled and nice colleagues, but also further evolved my programming skills to a higher level, with a lot of useful feedback from the company.
- Tested and debugged their functions through XUnit with:
 - Unittesting
 - Acceptance tests
 - Integration tests
- Today Infomedia uses the code I have worked with in their production.

Course Creator | App Academy

i June 2022 - August 2022

Sdr Havnegade 7, 6000 Kolding

- Creating and recording a Java Spring / Spring Boot online course with:
 - Presentations.
 - Assignments.
 - Quizzes.
- It has improved my ability to share, be resourceful and formulate knowledge to others on a technical level.
- The course is currently in use by App Academy.

Educational Tutoring | Save the Children

in November 2019 - April 2021

💎 Tagensvej 85D, 2200 København

- Voluntary work.
- Everyone from 8th/9th grade or high school students to newly started university students.
- The reason I volunteered was a desire to break negative social legacy and at the same time help spread knowledge.
- Many of the visiting pupils have been people with a different ethnic background than danish and without the possibility of tutoring help from home.

Music Tutor | Independent

- **March** 2015 December 2022
- Creating lessons, acquiring and teaching music pupils.
- Meeting the students' demands and expectations for their best experience and development based on the target group that they have belonged to in terms of personality and learning.
- Improved my communication ability and delivery of knowledge, as well as to work responsibly and independently.

EDUCATION

Computer Science | KEA - Copenhagen School of Design and Technology

September 2020 — January 2023

- Guldbergsgade 29E, 2200 København
- Education of code implementation, design patterns, various diagrams and project management, mostly with agile principles such as Scrum and XP.
- Fullstack programming and software development course:

- Java Spring Boot

- Hibernate

JavaScript

- Maven

- JDBC

- CSS

- JUnit - HTML

- MySQL

- Electives courses:
 - ASP.NET MVC with C#

- React Native with TypeScript

- IT operations

* Identity

entity * Redux

* Hardware

* Entity Framework

* Firebase

Haluwai

* CSHTML

* Store

* ITIL

* Security

- * SQLite
- Other courses such as business and technology.
- The focus has been on mixing theory and practical ability.
- An internship is included.
- Most of the education projects have involved collaboration.

Electric Engineering | DTU - The Technical University of Denmark

September 2019 – July 2020

Anker Engelunds Vej 1, 2800 Kgs. Lyngby

- Two terms of an electrical engineering bachelor.
- Containing courses of:
 - Digital design
 - Mathematics
 - Electronic circuit
- Included some programming introductions with:
 - Java
 - C
 - VHDL
 - Verilog
- From this period I've gained a very professional immersion in engineering areas, both within hardware and software, as well as theory and high-level mathematics.

ABOUT ME

I see myself as a friendly, curious and open person who is social and enjoys everything creative and with logical elements mixed together.

In my spare time I either work on my side projects or spend time on some of my other interests, but can also have a quiet evening to relax.

An important thing for me is to keep evolving and learning new things and concepts that fascinate me.

I believe that life should be fun and exciting, but at the same time I want to have a good influence on others and the generations to come.

INTERESTS

Music Band Philosophy

Tablefootball/tennis

Billard/pool Gaming

Board games History

Politic Fitness